

# Pieter Bikkel

## Full Stack Developer

Vorden, Netherlands

+31 6 16 46 01 71

□ pieterbikkel@gmail.com

pieterbikkel.com

### Summary.

Software developer with years of experience in Design, development, testing, and maintenance of various Enterprise Web and Mobile Applications. Supportive and enthusiastic team player dedicated to streamlining the process and efficiently resolving project issues. Demonstrating the ability to learn and adapt quickly to new technologies. Extremely end customer focused with excellent verbal communication skills that allow understanding and aligning with customer's goals and expectations. Experienced working in high-pressure environments delivering and maintaining mission-critical systems. Demonstrated ability to work independently and undertake research to find an ideal solution for a complex problem in a defined time frame.

## Work experience

#### Software Developer

2020-12 - Present

B302

- Maintaining Dutch government iOS apps for the public healthcare.
- Building a new React application for the police and ambulance to audit calls.
- Building a new Study Abroad React application for the HAN, University of applied sciences.

### IT configuration management

2018-06 - Present

Bronkhorst High-Tech

• Configuring, replacing and wiping computers for users within the company.

### **Education**

#### **Bachelor Of Science In Computer Science**

2020-09 - Present

HAN, University of applied sciences

#### **Subjects Covered**

- Networks
- Databases
- Data Structures
- Software Design
- Interface Design

- Web Technologies
- Operating Systems
- Software Engineering
- Security and Encryption
- Software Project Management

## Senior General Secondary Education, **Nature & Technology**

#### **Baudartius College**

English

 Dutch • Mathematics for scientific studies

· Advanced mathematics

Computer Science

Physics

Chemistry

#### Skills —

**Build Systems** 

Jenkins

Maven

**Version Control Systems** 

Git

**Code Hosting Services** 

Github

Bitbucket

Gitlab

**Operating Systems** 

macOS

Windows

• Linux (Ubuntu)

Google Workspace

Office Suite

• iWork

Microsoft Office

**Databases** 

MongoDB

MSSQL

MySQL

Neo4i

**Programming Languages** 

Objective-C

Javascript

 Swift Java

Development /

**Environment Tools** 

Xcode

• PHP

MS Visual Studio

Intellij IDEA

• Figma

Azure data studio

Zeplin

## **Generic Development Skills**

Networking

Unit Testing

· Code Reviews

Virtualization

Cloud Services

Source Control

Data Structures

· Algorithm Design

Operating Systems

· Agile Methodologies

· Object-oriented Design

Continuous Integration

· Planning and Estimation

• Open Source Contribution